STACIE D. SUMMERS

Cookeville, TN 38501 ◆ (618)201-4724 ◆ sdsummers921@gmail.com

A skilled technical and customer service professional with over 16 years of experience in retail, healthcare, and hospitality spaces. Graduate of Computer Programming 2-year program looking to further grow career in a position to utilize both client facing and technical skillsets. Proven track record leading and developing highly engaged teams. A passionate and action-orientated service professional who takes complete ownership of the customer service experience.

SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

Client Relationship Management
Project Management
Strategic Planning
Visual Studio
Python
HTML5 and CSS

Process Development & Implementation
Customer Service
Hardware/Software Certification
Object Oriented Programming
C#
Full Stack Web Development

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RELATIENT — Cookeville, TN: Position eliminated due to reduction in force

Technical Support Analyst II, 2022-2023

- ♦ Consistently resolved cases over the 200 minimum case per month quota: typically, 250 or more for technical support cases including data verification, user additions and management, education for clients, database queries, and code analysis.
- Reduced the need for assistance from programming and data integration teams by using knowledge of Perl and SQL queries, which reduced the overall resolve time for cases.
- Facilitated deep dive issue resolution in a timely manner to increase customer satisfaction. Average time to resolution reduced from 4 days to 2 days.
- ♦ Conducted regular audits and review of internal data resulting in the identification of an internal reporting flaw. Recommended and implemented a modification to improve overall accuracy of our KPIs and internal metrics.
- Maintained high first-time resolution rate with exceptional customer survey responses.
- ◆ Led Client Education sessions to improve customer experience with product when knowledge gaps were identified through case research.
- ◆ Standardization of training for technical support analysists.

WILDWOOD RESORT & MARINA. — Granville, TN

Concierge Manager, 2021-2022

- ◆ Drove change initiatives to increase customer satisfaction by creating quality standards including scripting for telecommunications and in-person guest relations.
- ◆ Creation and deployment of resort-wide annual review system to evaluate and elevate employee performance. Responsible for Annual Employee Reviews and Evaluations for Concierge Representatives.
- Creation and development of a standardized training program to ensure consistent guest experience and reduction of reservation errors.
- ♦ Implemented multiple process changes to increase guest and customer satisfaction by reducing multiple department frictions which negatively affected guest experiences and outcomes.

STACIE D. SUMMERS Page 2

• Successful implementation of cross training program to increase productivity and reduction of staffing deficiencies across multiple departments while also reducing labor costs during winter season.

- ◆ Implemented a new promotional structure program based on service promotion to increase productivity and employee engagement.
- Instilled best practices for computer use by employees throughout resort to enhance cyber security.
- ♦ Head quarterly staff meetings and weekly management meetings

WABASH GENERAL HOSPITAL. — Mount Carmel, IL

Orthopedic Scribe, 2019 - 2022

- ◆ Top performing scribe for WGH Orthopedic department, specializing in appointments for evaluation of the spine and osteoporosis screenings/treatments, and utilized as training resource with new hires.
- Effectively reduced denied claims and maximized reimbursements for by educating staff on proper code usage and pre-authorization practices.
- Creation and implementation of training documentation, scribe templates, and best practices for specialized appointments for Better Bones osteoporosis clinic.
- Played integral role in reducing patient appointment wait times while upholding excellent patient satisfaction and outcomes.

COOKEVILLE REGIONAL MEMORIAL HOSPITAL. — Cookeville, TN

Patient Registration Representative II, 2018 - 2019

- Recognized as top-level representative promoted from level I to level II within first six months of hire date.
- ◆ Holds record-setting collection for ER copays in 1 month totaling \$10,000, breaking previous record by approximately \$4,000 and collaborated with team to consistently ensure completion of Registration Department collection goals.
- Responsible for managing patient information and insurance verification quickly and efficiently for ER and after-hours hospital admissions to reduce delays in patient testing, treatment, and transfers.
- ♦ Monitor patient tracking application and work closely with multiple departments to prioritize registration of patients based on triage status and improve patient care.
- ◆ CHAA certification completed.

HEALTH FIRST. — Viera, FL

Service Access Representative II, 2017 – 2018

- ◆ Identified as top performer in quality and utilized as training resource with new representatives.
- Fundamental in deployment of in-person scheduling at satellite facilities.
- Utilized Yellow Belt Six Sigma training to reduce time spent on calls for MRI scheduling and shorten time span for scheduling available MRI appointments.
- Monitor call que and work as cohesive member of call center scheduling team to reduce call wait times for patients scheduling diagnostic tests.
- Educate patients on proper procedures and preparation for diagnostic testing to ensure best outcomes of patient testing.
- Actively participate in weekly staff meetings to devise ways to meet department goals.

STACIE D. SUMMERS Page 3

LEE N SHELDON, DMD. — Melbourne, FL

Treatment Coordinator, 2014 - 2017

• Managed schedule and inbound inquiries for new patients to increase number of weekly new patient appointments by 25% while simultaneously increasing appointment for patient treatment.

- Coordinated monthly educational presentations to potential patients.
- Performed and tracked diagnostic testing to aid in periodontal evaluation of patient. Developed effective and affordable treatment plans based on results of evaluation to assist patients in receiving necessary and desired treatments.
- Responsible for the training of staff to properly and efficiently complete front desk job requirements.
- ◆ Acted as patient liaison for claims submitted to insurance companies to maximize reimbursement to patients.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

VOLUNTEER STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE — Cookeville, TN

Graduated 2021

- ◆ Computer Programming
- ◆ Acted as Project Manager for all group projects
- ◆ Served as Secretary of VSCC Cyber Security Club

2019 - 2020

◆ Pursued Associates of Science in Healthcare Information Management

TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY — Cookeville, TN

2018 - 2019

◆ Pursued Associates of Science in Computer Science

EASTERN FLORIDA STATE COLLEGE — Melbourne, FL

2016

◆ Pursued Associates of Science in Computer Information Technologies

LEAN SIX SIGMA YELLOW BELT CERTIFIED

2016 - Health First.

• Project member tasked with data collection process to assist in the reduction of average wait time for scheduled MRIs across Health First health systems.

PC PRO HARDWARE/SOFTWARE CERTIFICATION— Cookeville, TN

2020

◆ Completed PC Pro A+ Hardware/Software Certification

CERTIFIED HEALTHCARE ACCESS ASSOCIATE - Cookeville, TN

2020

◆ Completed CHAA Certification as part of continuing education at CRMC.